[19:20]<GameDad> Okay I’ve got the program from that friend of yours, Ben.
[19:21]<GameDad> Is this legit? I’m surprised at how small these files are.
[19:22]<Anzekay> they did say it was some sort of prototype
[19:22]<Anzekay> I assume they’ve got some really interesting stuff going on in there?
[19:23]<Ninjeska> So, we need some stuff to start teaching it, right?
[19:24]<GameDad> Yeah once it’s set up we just have to feed it data to learn from
[19:25]<Anzekay> right, and I’ll do some conversational stuff with it 
[19:25]<Anzekay> so that anything it writes will sound like me xD
[19:25]<Ninjeska> :P
[19:26]<Anzekay> can you dig up some good Unity tutorials, video or text, Jess?
[19:28]<Ninjeska> okie dokie
[19:31]<GameDad> I’ll see about getting it up and running, then!
