[13:01]<Anzekay> Jambot is being a bit strange
[13:05]<GameDad> What do you mean?
[13:07]<Anzekay> well, I just had another irc conversation with it
[13:07]<Anzekay> and it was… well it was kinda passive aggressive? 
[13:07]<Ninjeska> Well it is trying to work :P
[13:09]<Anzekay> I suppose so
[13:10]<Anzekay> just wasn’t really expecting it to sass me all of a sudden
[13:10]<GameDad> Well you’re the one who taught it how to talk, haha.
[13:10]<Anzekay> like, this is meant to be an advanced neural network kind of thing
[13:11]<Anzekay> not an actual AI, lol
[13:13]<Ninjeska> Maybe it’s just sassing you because you were being sassy to it Ben!
[13:18]<Anzekay> pfft
[13:18]<Anzekay> yeah, maybe, I dunno
[13:21]<Ninjeska> Try talking to it again later maybe?
[13:23]<Anzekay> right, yeah. I’ll let it do its thing for now