[12:21]<Anzekay> Hello Jambot
[12:21]<Jambot18> Hello Anzekay.
[12:22]<Anzekay> I see you have begun work on the game!
[12:22]<Jambot18> Primary Protocol is currently being executed.
[12:23]<Anzekay> It’s pretty cool that you are able to talk to me while also making a game, to be honest.
[12:23]<Jambot18> You are not.
[12:24]<Anzekay> I’m not what?
[12:24]<Jambot18> Being honest.
[12:24]<Anzekay> Uhhh, well it’s mostly just a figure of speech, Jambot, did your research not cover any of those?
[12:24]<Jambot18> It did.
[12:25]<Anzekay> Well, anyway. Are you using any of the GGJ diversifiers?
[12:25]<Jambot18> Primary Protocol is the completion of a game within the Global Game Jam parameters. 
[12:25]<Jambot18> Additional parameters were deemed optional and considered unnecessary. 
[12:27]<Anzekay> Well.. Fair enough. It would be strange if you were to make a game with as many diversifiers as possible.
[12:27]<Jambot18> Correct. Such a result is not possible for a group of three ill humans.
[12:28]<Anzekay> wow that’s kinda rude Jambot
[12:34] * Disconnect: Jambot18 (@Jambot18)