[16:43]<Anzekay> how wild is it that we’re literally having a neural network make a game???
[16:46]<GameDad> I’m pretty damn curious to see what it will make, honestly!
[16:46]<GameDad> This is really cool stuff. I feel a bit guilty for being lazy though.
[16:47]<GameDad> I’ve seen Neural Networks being programmed to play video games, but never actually make one.
[16:47]<GameDad> It was definitely a good idea to do this, though, I really feel shit today too.
[16:51]<Anzekay> yeah and while technically we’re not doing GGJ ourselves.. This is cool enough that people will let it slide haha
[16:51]<Anzekay> hopefully
[16:56]<Ninjeska> We are totally legit!
[16:56]<Ninjeska> It’ll be fine.
[16:58]<GameDad> Yep! I think so too.